<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>National News | National News Headlines – Yahoo India News</title>
<link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/national/</link>
<description>Latest India news headlines from Yahoo India News. Find news in videos, pictures &amp; in-depth coverage on india from our national news section.</description>
<language>en-IN</language>
<copyright>Copyright (c) 2014 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved</copyright>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:37:24 +0530</pubDate>
<ttl>5</ttl>
<image>
<title>National News | National News Headlines – Yahoo India News</title>
<link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/national/</link>
<url>http://l.yimg.com/rz/d/yahoo_news_en-IN_s_f_p_bestfit_news.png</url>
</image>
<item><title>Home Secretary releases two publications of BPR and D</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): Union Home Secretary Anil Goswami on Thursday released two publications of Bureau of Police Research and Development (BPR and D) on "Data on Police Organisations in India 2013" and "Compendium on Projects of National Police Mission''.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/home-secretary-releases-two-publications-bpr-d-170724263.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:37:24 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">home-secretary-releases-two-publications-bpr-d-170724263</guid></item><item><title>Kejriwal violated Model Code of Conduct in Gujarat: EC</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): The Election Commission on Thursday said that Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) chief Arvind Kejriwal violated the Model Code of Conduct during his road show in Gujarat. "In the reports which have been given to us, it is written that the model code of conduct was not followed," said Election Commissioner H.S. Brahma. AAP workers on Wednesday fought pitched battles with BJP activists outside the saffron party headquarters here hours after AAP chief Arvind Kejriwal was detained briefly in Gujarat. The Gujarat Police stated that Kejriwal had not taken permission from them to hold a road show.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kejriwal-violated-model-code-conduct-gujarat-ec-170724402.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:37:24 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kejriwal-violated-model-code-conduct-gujarat-ec-170724402</guid></item><item><title>AAP leader Manish Sisodia's car attacked in Gujarat</title><description>Himmatnagar (Gujarat), March 6 (ANI): Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) leader Manish Sisodia's car was on Thursday attacked by unidentified men in Himmatnagar area of Sabarkantha district in Gujarat. Sisodia has alleged that his car was alleged by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) workers.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/aap-leader-manish-sisodias-car-attacked-gujarat-170724686.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:37:24 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">aap-leader-manish-sisodias-car-attacked-gujarat-170724686</guid></item><item><title>India hopes for peaceful resolution to Ukranian crisis: NSA Shiv Shankar Menon</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): National Security Adviser (NSA) Shiv Shankar Menon said that India hopes the crisis in Ukraine would be settled peacefully after satisfactory solution of the broader issues concerning the region. "We are watching what is happening in Ukraine with some concern. We would hope that whatever internal issues are there within Ukraine are settle peacefully. Crimea's parliament has voted to join Russia and its Moscow-backed government set a referendum within 10 days on the decision in a dramatic escalation of the crisis over the Ukrainian Black Sea peninsula.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/india-hopes-peaceful-resolution-ukranian-crisis-nsa-shiv-170724969.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:37:24 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">india-hopes-peaceful-resolution-ukranian-crisis-nsa-shiv-170724969</guid></item><item><title>Who has died from your family, Mulayam asks media</title><description>Lucknow, March 6 (IANS) Samajwadi Party chief Mulayam Singh Yadav Thursday tried to play down the death of patients as a result of the doctors' strike, and asked journalists if anyone had died from their families.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/died-family-mulayam-asks-media-163404937.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 22:04:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">died-family-mulayam-asks-media-163404937</guid></item><item><title>Probe BJP intimidation, AAP tells poll panel</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) The Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) Thursday urged the Election Commission to order an independent probe into what it said were attempts by the BJP to intimidate it. Citing at least four incidents of Wednesday, the AAP told the poll panel that there appeared to be a concerted attempt by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) "to attack and intimate the AAP". Gupta urged the Election Commission to institute an independent inquiry to probe these incidents. "Kindly investigate this issue and take prompt and strict action to ensure that such attacks, violence and intimidation (are) not repeated." The AAP alleged that it were BJP members who attacked its members from inside the BJP office here Wednesday with stones, bricks, furniture, sticks and bottles when the AAP held a demonstration outside.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/probe-bjp-intimidation-aap-tells-poll-panel-155008404.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 21:20:08 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">probe-bjp-intimidation-aap-tells-poll-panel-155008404</guid></item><item><title>Indian Diplomat in Saudi Arabia Sibi George wins S.K. Singh award</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): Vice President Hamid Ansari on Thursday presented "3rd S.K. Singh Award for Excellence in Indian Foreign Service" to Sibi George, the 1993 batch officer of Indian Foreign Service (IFS). Addressing on the occasion, he said that Late S.K. Singh was a distinguished diplomat and was his senior in IFS, and also extended his felicitations and best wishes to Manju Singh and the S.K. Singh Memorial Trust for keeping alive the rich legacy of Singh through the institution of this Award.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/indian-diplomat-saudi-arabia-sibi-george-wins-k-143928155.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 20:09:28 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">indian-diplomat-saudi-arabia-sibi-george-wins-k-143928155</guid></item><item><title>Atomic Energy Dept. clarifies on media reports regarding UCIL operations in Jh'khand</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): The Department of Atomic Energy on Thursday clarified that recent reports published by certain sections of media about the 'adverse radiation effects' of operations of Uranium Corporation of India Ltd. (UCIL) in Jaduguda, East Singhbhum district of Jharkhand are speculative, misleading and are not based on scientific facts. This clarification also applies on similar reports appeared earlier in print as well as electronic media attributing various ailments of the people living in Jaduguda region to the operations of UCIL. UCIL is a responsible organization, under the Department of Atomic Energy (DAE), Government of India, and is well aware of its responsibility towards the workers, members of the public and the environment.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/atomic-energy-dept-clarifies-media-reports-regarding-ucil-143928362.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 20:09:28 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">atomic-energy-dept-clarifies-media-reports-regarding-ucil-143928362</guid></item><item><title>If AAP had any problem, it should have gone to EC: Kiran Bedi</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): Former IPS officer turned social activist Kiran Bedi on Thursday criticized the Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) over their protest outside the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) headquarters, and said that if the AAP had any grievance, then they should have gone to the Election Commission. "If they had to protest against the BJP, then they should have gone to the Jantar Mantar. Earlier today, AAP leader Ashutosh was taken into custody by the Delhi Police for questioning in connection to his role in clashes outside the BJP headquarters. AAP workers on Wednesday fought pitched battles with BJP activists outside the saffron party headquarters here hours after AAP chief Arvind Kejriwal was detained briefly in Gujarat.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/aap-had-problem-gone-ec-kiran-bedi-143928980.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 20:09:28 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">aap-had-problem-gone-ec-kiran-bedi-143928980</guid></item><item><title>Himachal BJP MP booked, caught taking cash on camera</title><description>Shimla, March 6 (IANS) The Himachal Pradesh Vigilance and Anti-Corruption Bureau Thursday booked sitting BJP parliamentarian Virender Kashyap who was allegedly caught accepting cash on camera. The Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) has retained the one-time MP from the Shimla (reserved) seat. "A case against Kashyap was registered under section 9 of the Prevention of Corruption Act," a police official told IANS. In November, the Himachal Pradesh High Court issued notice to Kashyap on a petition for quashing a police inquiry report giving a clean chit to him after he was allegedly caught accepting cash.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/himachal-bjp-mp-booked-caught-taking-cash-camera-140223933.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 19:32:23 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">himachal-bjp-mp-booked-caught-taking-cash-camera-140223933</guid></item><item><title>RSS meet in Bangalore, expansion plans on agenda</title><description>Bangalore, March 6 (IANS) The Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS) will chalk out plans to expand its activities across India at its annual meeting beginning here Friday. Clarifying that the three-day meeting had no political agenda and was not connected to the forthcoming general elections, the Sangh's publicity head Manmohan Vaidya told reporters Thursday that the meeting would also evaluate its programmes and performance in social domains. The meeting of the Sangh's highest body for policy formulation and decision-making - the Akhil Bharatiya Pratinidhi Sabha (ABPS) - is being held in the city after 12 years. Besides the Sangh's Sarsanghchalak (chief) Mohan Rao Bhagwat and Sarkaryavah (general secretary) Suresh Bhaiyyaji Joshi and a dozen office-bearers, about 1,400 representatives from across the country will participate in the meet.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/rss-meet-bangalore-expansion-plans-agenda-135408237.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 19:24:08 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">rss-meet-bangalore-expansion-plans-agenda-135408237</guid></item><item><title>Ahead of poll code, Congress on inauguration spree</title><description>Shimla, March 6 (IANS) Racing against the time, Congress ministers, both of the central and state governments, were in an inauguration spree in Himachal Pradesh just minutes before the mode code of conduct came into force Wednesday. In less than two hours, one central project was inaugurated, while the foundation stone of two others were laid. Quite naturally, the government is the target of the main opposition BJP, which has termed the actions politically motivated. "It's a black day in the democratic history of the state," remarked state BJP president Satpal Satti.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/ahead-poll-code-congress-inauguration-spree-132404614.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:54:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">ahead-poll-code-congress-inauguration-spree-132404614</guid></item><item><title>Israeli, German held with drugs in Goa</title><description>Panaji, March 6 (IANS) An Israeli and a German national were arrested Thursday in two separate incidents for possession of synthetic drugs near Chapora, a village in Goa infamous for drug trade, police said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/israeli-german-held-drugs-goa-131615484.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:46:15 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">israeli-german-held-drugs-goa-131615484</guid></item><item><title>Mukherjee to inaugurate Annual Innovation Exhibition tomorrow</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): President Pranab Mukherjee will inaugurate the Annual Innovation Exhibition tomorrow at the Sports Ground of Rashtrapati Bhavan. Since 2010, the National Innovation Foundation-India has been organizing an Innovation Exhibition in Rashtrapati Bhavan every year. This year's exhibition will showcase 41 innovative technologies including seven from students. The exhibition will be open to the public from March 7 to 13, 2014.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/mukherjee-inaugurate-annual-innovation-exhibition-tomorrow-131556230.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:45:56 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">mukherjee-inaugurate-annual-innovation-exhibition-tomorrow-131556230</guid></item><item><title>Kejriwal says there was development of Ambani and Adani, not of farmers in Gujarat</title><description>Gandhidam, March 6 (ANI): Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) chief Arvind Kejriwal on Thursday said that there was development in Gujarat but it was of Ambani's and Adani's. "There was growth in Gujarat but it was of Ambani's and Adani's. The farmers in Gujarat were decimated. The common man has suffered in Gujarat," said Kejriwal, who is in Gujarat to verify the development claims often made by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) prime ministerial candidate Narendra Modi.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kejriwal-says-development-ambani-adani-not-farmers-gujarat-131556323.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:45:56 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kejriwal-says-development-ambani-adani-not-farmers-gujarat-131556323</guid></item><item><title>President to inaugurate innovation exhibition Friday</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) Over 40 new-avatar technologies will be on display at the Annual Innovation Exhibition which President Pranab Mukherjee will inaugurate at Rashtrapati Bhavan here Friday, an official statement said. Since 2010, the exhibition is being organised every year at the sports ground of the president estate by the National Innovation Foundation (NIF), Rashtrapati Bhavan said in a statement Thursday. "This year's exhibition will showcase 41 innovative technologies, including seven from students.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/president-inaugurate-innovation-exhibition-friday-131214813.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:42:14 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">president-inaugurate-innovation-exhibition-friday-131214813</guid></item><item><title>Man held with heroin worth Rs.1.5 crore</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) A drug peddler has been arrested here with heroin valued at Rs.1.5 crore, police said Thursday. Ishwar Lal, 22, was arrested from east Delhi's Patparganj area Tuesday, when he had gone there to meet one of his clients to supply drugs. "About 1.1 kg of fine quality heroin worth Rs.1.5 crore in the international market was recovered from him," Additional Commissioner of Police Ravindra Yadav said. Police received a tip-off that a man would deliver a consignment of heroin to one of his contacts near Patparganj, he said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/man-held-heroin-worth-rs-1-5-crore-130804461.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:38:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">man-held-heroin-worth-rs-1-5-crore-130804461</guid></item><item><title>BJP caused troubles wherever it went: Rahul Gandhi</title><description>Bhiwandi, (Maharashtra), Mar. 6 (ANI): Congress Vice President Rahul Gandhi on Thursday said that wherever the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) went they created fights between people of different religion, castes and states and that they never spoke about the weak or the poor. But if the same money is given to a rich man, the money is not wasted but contributes in the progress of India," he said. Tell me the name of one single programme where the Congress has not been inclusive," he added. He further said that the people of party took the credit of the Congress's hard work.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bjp-caused-troubles-wherever-went-rahul-gandhi-130608492.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:36:08 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bjp-caused-troubles-wherever-went-rahul-gandhi-130608492</guid></item><item><title>Tamil Nadu won't allow field trials of GM crops: Jayalalithaa</title><description>Nagapattinam (Tamil Nadu), March 6 (IANS) Tamil Nadu Chief Minister J. Jayalalithaa Thursday said her government will not allow field trials of genetically modified (GM) crops in the state. She asserted that when the new government at the centre, in which AIADMK would be a part, assumes office after the general elections, the permission to field trials of GM crops would be cancelled. Jayalalithaa was addressing an election rally here, around 300 km from Chennai. Referring to the centre's recent decision to allow field trials of around 200 varieties of GM crops, she said it would make the multi-national seed companies happy and result in grief for farmers.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/tamil-nadu-wont-allow-field-trials-gm-crops-130404107.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:34:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">tamil-nadu-wont-allow-field-trials-gm-crops-130404107</guid></item><item><title>RSS meet begins, expansion plans on agenda</title><description>Bangalore, March 6 (IANS) The Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS) Thursday began its annual meeting here to chalk out plans for expanding its activities across India. Clarifying that the three-day meeting had no political agenda and was not connected to the general elections, RSS publicity head Manamohan Vaidya told reporters that the meeting would evaluate its programmes and performance in diverse social domains. The meeting of the Sangh's highest body for policy formulation and decision-making - the Akhil Bharatiya Pratinidhi Sabha (ABPS) is being held in the city after 12 years.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/rss-meet-begins-expansion-plans-agenda-125405618.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:24:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">rss-meet-begins-expansion-plans-agenda-125405618</guid></item><item><title>Doctors end their strike after Allahabad High Court's assurance of time bound probe</title><description>Kanpur, March 6 (ANI): Indian Medical Association (IMA) called off doctors' strike on Thursday after Allahabad High Court promised judicial inquiry in arrest of doctors after a scuffle with a legislator. Since this statement has been made by the High Court, we respect the decision of the Court," said Secretary General of IMA, Narendra Sahni. The doctors also decided to withdraw their stir after a delegation led by chairman of the action committee of IMA, Devendra Lal Chandani, met Samajwadi Party (SP) chief Mulayam Singh Yadav. Sahni stated that Yadav promised that 23 junior doctors, who were arrested over clash with police and supporters of a local legislator, will be released.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/doctors-end-strike-allahabad-high-courts-assurance-time-124109079.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:11:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">doctors-end-strike-allahabad-high-courts-assurance-time-124109079</guid></item><item><title>Former Congress leader Daggubati Purandeswari likely to join BJP</title><description>New Delhi, Mar. 6 (ANI): Former Congress leader Daggubati Purandeswari on Thursday showed her willingness to join the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) and is likely to join the party on Friday.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/former-congress-leader-daggubati-purandeswari-likely-join-bjp-124109158.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:11:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">former-congress-leader-daggubati-purandeswari-likely-join-bjp-124109158</guid></item><item><title>Woolmark company and Raymond announce launch of 'Cool Wool' in India</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): The Woolmark Company and Raymond have launched a complete new 'Cool Wool' collection, which was showcased during a fashion show at the Australian High Commission. In an effort to promote wool as a trans-seasonal fibre in India, fashion designer Gaurav Jai Gupta showcased a collection of more than 20 garments with contemporary styling, finesse and subtle designs. Peter Ackroyd, Global Strategic Advisor for The Woolmark Company said, "Raymond's Cool Wool menswear collection exemplifies the infinite possibilities of using wool.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/woolmark-company-raymond-announce-launch-cool-wool-india-124109946.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:11:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">woolmark-company-raymond-announce-launch-cool-wool-india-124109946</guid></item><item><title>20 disaster relief men to be honoured with PM's Medal</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) Twenty personnel of the National Disaster Response Force (NDRF) have been awarded the Prime Minister's Medal for their exemplary rescue work in natural disasters, including during the floods in Uttarakhand last year. "The nation faced numerous natural disasters in 2013 such as cloudburst in Uttarakhand, floods in Assam, cyclonic storm Phailin in Andhra Pradesh and Odisha. NDRF personnel saved lives of a large number of people in these calamities," the group said in a statement Thursday.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/20-disaster-relief-men-honoured-pms-medal-124004700.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 18:10:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">20-disaster-relief-men-honoured-pms-medal-124004700</guid></item><item><title>Sedition charges unacceptably harsh, tweets Omar Abdullah</title><description>Meerut, March 6 (ANI): Jammu and Kashmir Chief Minister Omar Abdullah on Thursday took to twitter to vent his anger over J-K students being charged with sedition by the Uttar Pradesh Police for cheering for Pakistan during the India versus Pakistan cricket match. Earlier today, Meerut Police filed a FIR against suspended Kashmiri students of a private university for alleged anti-national activities. Last Sunday, 67 Kashmiri students were suspended in Meerut, after they cheered the Pakistan cricket team which cruised to victory in the India-Pakistan Asia Cup match in Bangladesh.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/sedition-charges-unacceptably-harsh-tweets-omar-abdullah-120642544.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 17:36:42 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">sedition-charges-unacceptably-harsh-tweets-omar-abdullah-120642544</guid></item><item><title>Woman, lover get death for killing seven in Haryana</title><description>The Rohtak district and sessions court awarded the death sentence to 23-year-old Sonam and her 24-year-old boyfriend Naveen Kumar for killing seven members of her family at Kabulpur village, 20 km from here. The victims were Sonam's parents, a teenaged brother, her 70-year-old grandmother and three cousins, all under 12 years.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/woman-lover-death-killing-seven-haryana-120211999.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 17:32:11 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">woman-lover-death-killing-seven-haryana-120211999</guid></item><item><title>Kashmiri students in UP face sedition charge for cheering Pakistan</title><description>Srinagar, March 6 (IANS) Kashmiri students expelled from a Uttar Pradesh university after they were accused of celebrating Pakistan cricket team's victory over India Thursday alleged victimisation by administration officials and police. Kashmiri students of Swami Vivekanand Subharti University (SVSU) in Meerut said 67 of them were forced to leave the college after the administration called police to ensure their eviction from the hostel. The students were accused of celebrating the victory of Pakistan cricket team in a crucial match of Asia Cup championship in Dhaka. "When the match took a different turn after Shahid Afridi's batting, some of our friends also started shouting as a reaction.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kashmiri-students-face-sedition-charge-cheering-pakistan-115608277.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 17:26:08 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kashmiri-students-face-sedition-charge-cheering-pakistan-115608277</guid></item><item><title>BJP complains, poll panel serves notice to AAP</title><description>The Election Commission in Delhi Thursday issued a notice to the Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) following clashes outside the BJP headquarters here Wednesday. Bharatiya Janata Party leaders meanwhile lodged a complaint with the Election Commission over the protest the AAP staged outside the BJP office a day earlier, triggering clashes. Ankur Garg, Chief Nodal Officer of the Delhi Election Commission, told IANS that the notice was issued for holding the street protest without permission. Bharatiya Janata Party leader Mukhtar Abbas Naqvi said: "AAP members are trying to hijack democracy and through anarchy want to harm the democratic structure of the country.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bjp-complains-poll-panel-serves-notice-aap-110604228.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:36:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bjp-complains-poll-panel-serves-notice-aap-110604228</guid></item><item><title>BJP-AAP clashes: Shazia Ilmi taken for questioning by Delhi Police</title><description>New Delhi, Mar. 6 (ANI): Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) leader Shazia Ilmi was taken into custody by the Delhi Police for questioning in connection to her role in clashes outside the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) office. "My name is in the FIR so the police is taking me to the station. I am abiding with them," Ilmi told reporters outside her home.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bjp-aap-clashes-shazia-ilmi-taken-questioning-delhi-110501645.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:35:01 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bjp-aap-clashes-shazia-ilmi-taken-questioning-delhi-110501645</guid></item><item><title>Kejriwal accuses Gujarat Government of grabbing land of farmers</title><description>Rajkot, (Gujarat), Mar. 6 (ANI): Former Delhi Chief Minister Arvind Kejriwal on Thursday slammed the Gujarat Government and accused them of threatening and grabbing the land of farmers. Kejriwal is in Gujarat to verify the development claims often made by the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) prime ministerial candidate Narendra Modi. "It seems that progress for the Congress and the BJP means torturing the farmers by snatching their lands. A land scam is taking place, basically the Sikh groups own one lakh acre land and its estimated value is worth 40 billion to 50 billion rupees, they want to grab land at any cost, this land scam is getting bigger," said Kejriwal.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kejriwal-accuses-gujarat-government-grabbing-land-farmers-110501472.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:35:01 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kejriwal-accuses-gujarat-government-grabbing-land-farmers-110501472</guid></item><item><title>Parrikar's budget helps Ramdev, RSS in Goa: Congress</title><description>Panaji, March 6 (IANS) Chief Minister Manohar Parrikar has made budgetary provisions for saffronisation of Goa by allowing Yoga guru Ramdev and the RSS to set up bases in the state, the Congress Thursday said. Addressing a press conference in Panaji, state Congress president John Fernandes Thursday said that the BJP government has laid the red carpet for Ramdev and Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh ideologue Indresh Kumar, and questioned how announcements made in the budget have already been made in the public domain months earlier. "NGOs owing affiliation to the Sangh Parivar are being indirectly promoted by the chief minister in Goa.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/parrikars-budget-helps-ramdev-rss-goa-congress-104205943.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">parrikars-budget-helps-ramdev-rss-goa-congress-104205943</guid></item><item><title>Ashutosh taken into custody for questioning by Delhi Police</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) leader Ashutosh on Thursday was taken into custody by the Delhi Police for questioning in connection to his role in clashes outside the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) headquarters. "I am a law abiding citizen, if the police wants me to co operate in the investigation then I will," said Ashutosh. Delhi Police had named Ashutosh, Shazia Ilmi, Prof Anand Kumar and several other AAP workers in its FIR filed in Parliament Street Police Station, which says that the party workers illegally gathered outside BJP headquarters in Delhi.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/ashutosh-taken-custody-questioning-delhi-police-102255668.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 15:52:55 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">ashutosh-taken-custody-questioning-delhi-police-102255668</guid></item><item><title>No place for violence in democracy: Sibal</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) Criticising clashes between AAP and BJP workers at the latter's office here Wednesday, Congress leader and Law Minister Kapil Sibal has said there is no place for violence in democracy. Aam Aadmi Party members held a demonstration Wednesday outside the Bharatiya Janata Party's headquarters here after police briefly detained AAP leader Arvind Kejriwal in Gujarat Wednesday. The protest turned ugly and members of the two parties clashed outside the BJP office. Speaking on the incident Thursday, Sibal, however, did not name either of the two parties as responsible.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/no-place-violence-democracy-sibal-102216318.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 15:52:16 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">no-place-violence-democracy-sibal-102216318</guid></item><item><title>SC defers hearing on Centre's plea against TN govt. decision to release Rajiv Gandhi's killer</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): The Supreme Court on Thursday deferred the hearing on the Centre's petition challenging the Tamil Nadu government's decision to release four convicts in the former prime minister Rajiv Gandhi assassination case. An apex court bench headed by Justice P. Sathasivam will now take up the matter on March 26. On February 27, the Supreme Court had earlier stayed the decision of the Tamil Nadu government to release the four convicts in the case. Acting on a petition filed by the Centre, the apex court had earlier issued a notice to the Tamil Nadu government restraining it from releasing the convicts and directed it to maintain status quo until further orders.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/sc-defers-hearing-centres-plea-against-tn-govt-092538292.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:55:38 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">sc-defers-hearing-centres-plea-against-tn-govt-092538292</guid></item><item><title>Footage tells a different story but AAP politics based on lies: Arun Jaitley</title><description>New Delhi, Mar. 6 (ANI): Reacting to the case filed against Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) members, Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) leader Arun Jailtey on Thursday said that the footage that captured their pitched battles with BJP activists might be saying a different story but false propaganda and lies had become an integral part of the AAP politics. "It is a routine procedure that whenever we go for campaigns, the Election Commission subjects every party to searches in order to make sure that money is not transported. So, this non detention of Arvind Kejriwal was nothing to make a fuss about," said Jaitley.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/footage-tells-different-story-aap-politics-based-lies-092538013.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:55:38 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">footage-tells-different-story-aap-politics-based-lies-092538013</guid></item><item><title>Students should have behaved like sportsmen not politicians: Mustafa Kamal</title><description>Srinagar, Mar. 6 (ANI): Reacting to the FIR lodged against Kashmiri students in Meerut, National Conference (NC) Party leader Mustafa Kamal on Thursday said that what the students had done was wrong as they should have behaved like sportsmen instead of behaving like politicians and that religion taught one to be faithful to one's own country and not disrespect it. I got the information that fir has been lodged against the students, and if a FIR has been lodged then it means that somebody has been offended. Meerut Police today filed a FIR against suspended Kashmiri students of a private university for alleged anti-national activities.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/students-behaved-sportsmen-not-politicians-mustafa-kamal-092538568.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:55:38 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">students-behaved-sportsmen-not-politicians-mustafa-kamal-092538568</guid></item><item><title>Doctors run parallel medical services amid strike in UP</title><description>Varanasi, Mar. 6 (ANI): Doctors in Varanasi have started running a parallel Out Patient Department (OPD) centres in order to attend to the suffering patients while they continue their strike at the same time. On Thursday, doctors were seen attending to the patients at the Institute of Medical Sciences (IMS), Banaras Hindu University (BHU). A senior doctor at the IMS at Banaras Hindu University, Om Shankar said that they shall continue fighting for their rights as well as serve the poor. "Our work is to serve people and we are fighting for the poor, we want to ensure that the poor do not face any problem and that is why we are running a parallel OPD, but we are protesting as well as working, parallel OPD, emergency, ICU (Intensive Care Unit) is being run, we are not doing anything that causes problems to people," he said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/doctors-run-parallel-medical-services-amid-strike-092538910.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:55:38 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">doctors-run-parallel-medical-services-amid-strike-092538910</guid></item><item><title>Kiran Kumar Reddy moves to SC against Andhra bifurcation</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (ANI): Former Andhra Pradesh Chief Minister Kiran Kumar Reddy on Thursday filed a petition in the Supreme Court against the decision of the Central Government to carve out a separate state of Telangana from Andhra Pradesh.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kiran-kumar-reddy-moves-sc-against-andhra-bifurcation-092538196.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:55:38 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kiran-kumar-reddy-moves-sc-against-andhra-bifurcation-092538196</guid></item><item><title>Poll panel seeks police report on violence</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) The Election Commission Thursday directed Delhi Police to submit a report on the AAP-BJP clash here Wednesday. "Police have been asked to name all the party workers who violated the model code of conduct," Delhi's Chief Electoral Officer Vijay Dev told IANS. "If party workers are found to be guilty, the party can be de-recognized," he added. On Wednesday, clashes erupted after AAP members staged a noisy protest outside the BJP headquarters here to denounce the brief detention of AAP leader Arvind Kejriwal in Gujarat.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/poll-panel-seeks-police-report-violence-090804151.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:38:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">poll-panel-seeks-police-report-violence-090804151</guid></item><item><title>Police arrest AAP members, AAP alleges bias</title><description>New Delhi, March 6 (IANS) Police have arrested 14 AAP members on charges of rioting outside the BJP office here and said Thursday they were looking two key AAP leaders. A police officer told IANS that the 14, including a professor, were taken into custody for the clashes that took place between AAP and BJP activists here Wednesday evening. The clashes followed a noisy demonstration the Aam Aadmi Party staged outside the Bharatiya Janata Party headquarters after police there briefly detained party leader Arvind Kejriwal in Gujarat Wednesday. The official said police were looking AAP leaders Shazia Ilmi and Ashutosh, both former journalists.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/police-arrest-aap-members-aap-alleges-bias-085004764.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 14:20:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">police-arrest-aap-members-aap-alleges-bias-085004764</guid></item></channel>
</rss>
<!-- fe930.global.media.sg3.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Thu Mar  6 18:11:11 UTC 2014 -->
