<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>National News | National News Headlines – Yahoo India News</title>
<link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/national/</link>
<description>Latest India news headlines from Yahoo India News. Find news in videos, pictures &amp; in-depth coverage on india from our national news section.</description>
<language>en-IN</language>
<copyright>Copyright (c) 2014 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved</copyright>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 23:38:04 +0530</pubDate>
<ttl>5</ttl>
<image>
<title>National News | National News Headlines – Yahoo India News</title>
<link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/national/</link>
<url>http://l.yimg.com/rz/d/yahoo_news_en-IN_s_f_p_bestfit_news.png</url>
</image>
<item><title>India dispatches two military aircraft for missing plane's search</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) India Friday dispatched a long endurance transport aircraft of Indian Air Force and a maritime surveillance aircraft of the navy to augment the search and rescue operations for the missing Malaysian airliner MH 370. An defence ministry release said that the government has pledged its full support to the Malaysian government in the ongoing multi-national search and rescue effort for the missing airliner. "The ministry of defence approved the deployment of Indian Armed Forces assets for the purpose. Accordingly a C-130 Hercules of the Indian Air Force and a long range Maritime Surveillance Aircraft P8 I of the Indian Navy have been dispatched to augment the search and rescue operations today (Friday)," the release said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/india-dispatches-two-military-aircraft-missing-planes-search-180804675.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 23:38:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">india-dispatches-two-military-aircraft-missing-planes-search-180804675</guid></item><item><title>Three priests arrested for murder in Bangalore seminary</title><description>Bangalore, March 21 (IANS) Police Friday achieved a breakthrough in the murder of rector Father Thomas last year at the St Peter's seminary here by arresting three priests for their alleged involvement in the crime. "It appears the accused have fatally assaulted the 65-year-old rector who caught them stealing documents from the seminary at Malleswaram (in the northwest suburbs)," Additional Police Commissioner (Crime) Pronob Mohanty told reporters here. "Arrest and sustained interrogation of seminary priest William Patrick, who was asleep in the adjacent room when the murder happened March 31 night, led us to other two priests - Ilyas and Peter - in the seminary for their involvement in the crime," Mohanty said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/three-priests-arrested-murder-bangalore-seminary-180621483.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 23:36:21 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">three-priests-arrested-murder-bangalore-seminary-180621483</guid></item><item><title>CBI registers preliminary enquiry in Rolls Royce bribery case</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) The Central Bureau of Investigation Friday registered a Preliminary Enquiry into the alleged bribery in the Rs. 18.8 crore deal for supply of aircraft engines to state-owned Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) by Britain's Rolls Royce.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/cbi-registers-preliminary-enquiry-rolls-royce-bribery-case-174405292.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 23:14:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">cbi-registers-preliminary-enquiry-rolls-royce-bribery-case-174405292</guid></item><item><title>Woman raped, murdered in Rajasthan</title><description>Jaipur, March 21 (IANS) A man raped a woman and then killed her by throwing her into a water tank in Rajasthan Friday, police said. She was alone when Ramdev Jat barged into her house and repeatedly raped her," said a police officer. The office said that Ramdev threw her body into a water tank and escaped.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/woman-raped-murdered-rajasthan-171622102.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 22:46:22 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">woman-raped-murdered-rajasthan-171622102</guid></item><item><title>Battling election anxiety, Congress faces desertions</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) The Congress, fighting negative public perception and with a demoralised cadre following a spate of opinion polls predicting a rout for the party in the coming elections, is having a tough time finding winnable candidates with some leaders unwilling to take the plunge and some others deserting the party to join its main rival BJP. Among the prominent Congress leaders who have joined the Bharatiya Janata Party in the run up to Lok Sabha elections are Satpal Maharaj, Jagdambika Pal and D. Purandeswari - three MPs who had won the 2009 election as Congress nominees. Party veteran and former union minister Buta Singh, who was home minister in the government of prime minister Rajiv Gandhi, has joined the Samajwadi Party.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/battling-election-anxiety-congress-faces-desertions-144405868.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 22:38:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">battling-election-anxiety-congress-faces-desertions-144405868</guid></item><item><title>Bank employee's relative killed in Delhi house</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) A woman relative of a private bank employee was battered to death with a blunt object and his two-year-old son injured by some unidentified assailants at a house here, police said Friday. The incident came to light around 8 p.m. Thursday when Arvinder Singh, 32, returned to his Uttam Nagar house in west Delhi with his wife Amarpreet Kaur, 27. The deceased, identified as Inderjeet Kaur, 45, was a distant relative and used to come to his house to take care of his son when the couple were away. Arvinder works in a private bank in Gurgaon, Haryana.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bank-employees-relative-killed-delhi-house-162616084.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 21:56:16 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bank-employees-relative-killed-delhi-house-162616084</guid></item><item><title>Argument on charges against BSP MP to be heard Saturday</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) A court here fixed Saturday to hear argument on charges in a case against Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP) MP Dhananjay Singh and his wife for torturing their maid, leading to her death. Additional Sessions Judge Lokesh Kumar Sharma Friday posted the argument on charges for Saturday. The MP's counsel S.P.M. Tripathi, while requesting the court to release his client on bail, has told the court last month that the witnesses were already granted protection by police and there was no chance for his client to influence them. The court had however rejected the bail plea of the MP, accused of destroying evidence to shield his wife, who was arrested for torturing her maid leading to her death.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/argument-charges-against-bsp-mp-heard-saturday-161005138.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 21:40:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">argument-charges-against-bsp-mp-heard-saturday-161005138</guid></item><item><title>Park Street gang rape victim hopes for justice too</title><description>Kolkata, March 21 (IANS) Elated at the verdicts in the Mumbai gangrape incidents, the Park Street rape victim Friday hoped justice would also prevail in her case. "Its amazing that the verdict in the Mumbai case has come through. With prayers in my heart and hope...that is all that keeps me going," the victim told IANS here, urging her name be used. A Mumbai court Friday awarded life sentences to four men convicted for gang-raping a 19-year-old call centre employee in the Shakti Mills Complex on July 31, 2013.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/park-street-gang-rape-victim-hopes-justice-too-155808783.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 21:28:08 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">park-street-gang-rape-victim-hopes-justice-too-155808783</guid></item><item><title>6.5 magnitude earthquake hits Nicobar Islands</title><description>Andaman and Nicobar, Mar. 21 (ANI): A 6.3 magnitude earthquake struck in the sea in Andaman and Nicobar Islands on Friday.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/6-5-magnitude-earthquake-hits-nicobar-islands-153502505.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 21:05:02 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">6-5-magnitude-earthquake-hits-nicobar-islands-153502505</guid></item><item><title>Sharmila promises brother Jagan Reddy will begin era of development</title><description>Giddarulu, Mar. 21 (ANI): Affirming that Y S R Congress Party president YS Jagan Mohan Reddy will turn a new leaf in the state polity in terms of development and welfare measures with his vision and programmes, Reddy's sister, Y.S Sharmila, has appealed to the voters to pronounce their verdict decisively in the ensuing elections to enable the Party to have a say in the formation of government at the Centre. As part of her YSR Praja Garjana electioneering she said "We have seen the dark age of Chandrababu Naidu and the reversal of that period by YSR regime which was followed by a slide into backwardness after the death of YSR. "YS Jagan Mohan Reddy is the need of the hour that can steer the state towards development, and ensure that all sections of the people are happy as he has a vision like YSR who balanced welfare and development," said Sharmila, while addressing a public meeting here on Friday.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/sharmila-promises-brother-jagan-reddy-begin-era-development-152127477.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:51:27 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">sharmila-promises-brother-jagan-reddy-begin-era-development-152127477</guid></item><item><title>Kejriwal expels two party members for allegedly offering tickets to contest polls in exchange for bribes</title><description>New Delhi, Mar. 21 (ANI): Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) Chief Arvind Kejriwal expelled two prominent members on Friday for allegedly offering tickets to contest in the upcoming general election in exchange for bribes. Kejriwal expelled Convener of the party in Awadh, Aruna Singh and a treasurer of the party in the district of Hardoi in Uttar Pradesh. So, on the account of the evidence we have gathered, today we are expelling the convenor of Awadh zone, Aruna Singh and Ashok who was the treasurer of Hardoi," said Kejriwal.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/kejriwal-expels-two-party-members-allegedly-offering-tickets-152127691.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:51:27 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">kejriwal-expels-two-party-members-allegedly-offering-tickets-152127691</guid></item><item><title>Jaswant's wish to contest from Barmer dashed by BJP</title><description>Barmer (Rajasthan), Mar 21, (ANI): Senior Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) leader Jaswant Singh has been denied Lok Sabha ticket from Barmer.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/jaswants-wish-contest-barmer-dashed-bjp-152127520.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:51:27 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">jaswants-wish-contest-barmer-dashed-bjp-152127520</guid></item><item><title>BJP only interested in inducting discards of other parties: Tyagi</title><description>New Delhi, Mar 21, (ANI): Janata Dal United (JD-U) leader K C Tyagi on Friday negated the fact that N K Singh who has resigned from the party will have any bearing on the party's prospects. "While the founder of the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) L K Advani, former BJP president Murli Manohar Joshi, Jaswant Singh and Uma Bharti are all unhappy, and on the other hand they (BJP) is more interested in inducting leaders from other parties who has been discarded,"Tyagi said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bjp-only-interested-inducting-discards-other-parties-tyagi-152044467.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:50:44 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bjp-only-interested-inducting-discards-other-parties-tyagi-152044467</guid></item><item><title>Ten women labourers drown in Rajasthan</title><description>Jaipur, March 21 (IANS) Ten women drowned when a boat they had boarded to cross a river capsized in Rajasthan Friday, police said. The mishap occurred in Tonk district's Deoli town, some 150 km from Jaipur. "The victims were labourers who were crossing Banas river on a boat to reach a construction site. The boat capsized following which all the women and the boatman fell into the river," said a police officer.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/ten-women-labourers-drown-rajasthan-151004939.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:40:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">ten-women-labourers-drown-rajasthan-151004939</guid></item><item><title>Realtor officials booked for destroying crop, thrashing farmer</title><description>Gurgaon, March 21 (IANS) Senior officials of realtor Vatika India Next here were booked for damaging ready-to-harvest mustard crop and beating up a farmer, police said Friday. Company officers Jamal Khan and Rajbir Singh along with 15-20 unidentified people were booked under sections 447 (mischief with property), 427 (causing damage to property), 323 (thrashing, beating), 506 (threatening with life) and 34 (common intent) of the Indian Penal Code. Rajesh of Shikohpur village here had complained to the police that employees of Vatika India Next company destroyed his mustard crop cultivated on more than half an acre of land in Sikanderpur village. "Company officers Jamal Khan and Rajbir Singh came with three policemen and 15-20 bouncers and crushed the crop with four JCB machines," Rajesh said in his complaint.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/realtor-officials-booked-destroying-crop-thrashing-farmer-145804707.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:28:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">realtor-officials-booked-destroying-crop-thrashing-farmer-145804707</guid></item><item><title>High court orders retrial against Himachal CM</title><description>Shimla, March 21 (IANS) The Himachal Pradesh High Court Friday ordered the retrial in the criminal defamation case against Chief Minister Virbhadra Singh. Hearing petitions of state Subordinate Services Selection Board former chairman S.M. Katwal, Justice D.C. Chaudhary directed the judicial magistrate in Una town for retrial. He challenged the judgment of sessions court which quashed the judicial magistrate's order to issue summons to Virbhadra Singh in two defamation cases. Katwal, who remained chairman of the board from 2000 to 2003, had filed criminal defamation cases alleging he was defamed by the speeches made by Virbhadra Singh at public meetings.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/high-court-orders-retrial-against-himachal-cm-145405772.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:24:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">high-court-orders-retrial-against-himachal-cm-145405772</guid></item><item><title>Congo national allegedly raped in Delhi</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) A 20-year-old Congolese national was allegedly raped here by two cloth merchants inside her house Friday afternoon, police said. She opened the gate and was busy in choosing the clothes when the men overpowered her and dragged her inside where she was raped," said a police officer as per the victim's statement. Deputy Commissioner of Police B.S. Jaiswal told IANS the police scrutinised the CCTV camera installed at the entrance of the building where the woman resides but no cloth merchants was seen in the footage available from Friday morning to 2 p.m. "As the woman is changing her statements, we are yet to ascertain if her allegation is right or wrong," said Jaiswal.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/congo-national-allegedly-raped-delhi-143804021.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 20:08:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">congo-national-allegedly-raped-delhi-143804021</guid></item><item><title>N K Singh parts ways with JD-U after being denied RS re-nomination</title><description>New Delhi, Mar 21, (ANI): Janata Dal (United) leader and former bureaucrat Nand Kishore Singh on Friday announced that he was leaving the party after being denied a re-nominated ticket to the Rajya Sabha. He indicated that he was in close touch with the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP). "Well I have already sent my resignation from the JD-U. I am certainly in conversation with the senior leadership of the BJP. People think, that for good reasons, the fact that I was not re-nominated for a second term in Rajya Sabha is the principle reason that I was upset, which is indeed true, as I was disappointed, as it was understandable, since I did a fairly good job to promote Bihar nationally and internationally," Singh said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/n-k-singh-parts-ways-jd-u-being-134632391.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 19:16:32 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">n-k-singh-parts-ways-jd-u-being-134632391</guid></item><item><title>Poll fever heats up in Delhi as AAP, BJP candidates file their nominations</title><description>New Delhi, Mar 21, (ANI): With days to go for the polls in Delhi, contestants from various political colours have started filing their nominations from representing their respective constituencies. Ram Mohan Gandhi, who is representing East Delhi constituency on behalf of Aam Aadmi Party (AAP), talked on stressing the need to build proper infrastructure in the area. "My agenda is to give relief to the residents of east Delhi with proper sanitation, clean air, parks.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/poll-fever-heats-delhi-aap-bjp-candidates-file-134632715.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 19:16:32 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">poll-fever-heats-delhi-aap-bjp-candidates-file-134632715</guid></item><item><title>Officer, three soldiers injured in Kashmir grenade blast</title><description>Jammu, March 21 (IANS) Four soldiers including an officer were injured in an accidental grenade explosion along the line of control (LoC) in Jammu district of Jammu and Kashmir Friday, said defence sources. According to the sources, the soldiers were training in Keri area of Akhnoor sector when four of them including a major were injured in an accidental grenade explosion. "The explosion occurred when troopers of Gurkha Regiment were undergoing training practice of grenade firing," a defence source said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/officer-three-soldiers-injured-kashmir-grenade-blast-131219021.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 18:42:19 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">officer-three-soldiers-injured-kashmir-grenade-blast-131219021</guid></item><item><title>Now, AAP to take on Sriramulu in Karnataka</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) The Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) Friday released its ninth list of candidates for the Lok Sabha polls and said it was fielding Shivakumar Giriyappa Malagi against the BJP's B. Sriramulu in Bellary in Karnataka in what is expected to be a high-profile contest. Sriramulu's BSR Congress, which he had floated after quitting the BJP, was merged with the saffron party recently despite senior leader Sushma Swaraj's expressing reservations over this. The BJP gave a ticket to Sriramulu in preference to incumbent J. Shantha.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/now-aap-sriramulu-karnataka-125618160.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 18:26:18 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">now-aap-sriramulu-karnataka-125618160</guid></item><item><title>Don't buckle under pressure in Italian marines case: Chandy</title><description>Thiruvananthapuram, March 21 (IANS) Kerala Chief Minister Oommen Chandy Friday urged Prime Minister Manmohan Singh to see that India does not budge under pressure from international agencies trying to get the two Italian marines accused of killing two Indian fishermen to escape without trial. "The incident that occurred when two Indian fishermen were killed by these two Italian marines was most gruesome and people in Kerala are closely watching the ongoing trial. Any decision by bowing to international pressure would be belittling the law of our land," said Chandy in his letter. The Kerala High Court and the Supreme Court have upheld the case and the latter has asked for a probe by the National Investigation Agency.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/dont-buckle-under-pressure-italian-marines-case-chandy-124622255.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 18:16:22 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">dont-buckle-under-pressure-italian-marines-case-chandy-124622255</guid></item><item><title>Rs.14 lakh in fake currency seized</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) The Border Security Force (BSF) recovered counterfeit Indian currency with a face value of Rs.13,99,500 near the Indo-Bangladesh border, an official said Friday.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/rs-14-lakh-fake-currency-seized-123617439.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 18:06:17 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">rs-14-lakh-fake-currency-seized-123617439</guid></item><item><title>Shiv Sena denies fielding candidates against Modi in Uttar Pradesh</title><description>Mumbai/New Delhi, Mar.21 (ANI): The Shiv Sena on Friday denied that it plans to field candidates against BJP prime ministerial candidate Narendra Modi and party president Rajnath Singh in Uttar Pradesh. Reportedly, Shiv Sena leader Sanjay Raut was quoted as saying that his party will announce candidates for general elections from Uttar Pradesh, including for Varanasi and Lucknow. Modi is contesting from the Varanasi constituency, while Rajnath Singh is contesting from Lucknow. We have just made an announcement that outside Maharashtra, Shiv Sena will fight elections.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/shiv-sena-denies-fielding-candidates-against-modi-uttar-114126100.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 17:37:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">shiv-sena-denies-fielding-candidates-against-modi-uttar-114126100</guid></item><item><title>Sibal lashes out at Modi, BJP for sidelining Advani</title><description>New Delhi, Mar 21, (ANI): Union Minister Kapil Sibal on Friday heaped scorn on the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) for its internal feud, following senior BJP leader Lal Krishna Advani's initial disinclination to contest from Gandhinagar. More such bickering within the BJP is set to unfold soon. It has been his (Modi's) idea to rule the country and ignore others, including the BJP. Perhaps, Modi has no idea that whenever, anyone any monarch had tried to rule the nation, the history has not been kind to them.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/sibal-lashes-modi-bjp-sidelining-advani-114126131.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 17:37:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">sibal-lashes-modi-bjp-sidelining-advani-114126131</guid></item><item><title>BJP leader Jaswant Singh denied LS ticket from Barmer</title><description>New Delhi, Mar.21 (ANI): The Central Election Committee of the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) decided on Friday not to give in to veteran leader Jaswant Singh's demand/request to grant him a ticket to contest the general elections from Rajasthan's Barmer District. Speculation is also rife that the RSS and Chief Minister Vasundhara Raje have had a say in denying Jaswant Singh the ticket. The rejection of Jaswant Singh comes soon after another leader L.K.Advani was told that he could only contest from Gandhinagar, instead of his preferred choice of Bhopal. The BJP has been facing an uproar lately for election ticket distribution, especially over the fielding of Advani.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bjp-leader-jaswant-singh-denied-ls-ticket-barmer-114126235.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 17:37:09 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bjp-leader-jaswant-singh-denied-ls-ticket-barmer-114126235</guid></item><item><title>BSF brings back farmer abducted by Bangladeshi criminals</title><description>Kolkata, March 21 (IANS) A two-month-long endeavour of the Border Security Force (BSF) bore fruit Friday when an Indian farmer, abducted and taken to Bangladesh by criminals, was brought back home, an official said.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/bsf-brings-back-farmer-abducted-bangladeshi-criminals-114211083.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 17:12:11 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">bsf-brings-back-farmer-abducted-bangladeshi-criminals-114211083</guid></item><item><title>Husband chains wife over alleged infidelity in Madhya Pradesh town</title><description>Chhatarpur (Madhya Pradesh), Mar.21 (ANI): Police in Madhya Pradesh's Chhattarpur town have confirmed registering a complaint against a husband who chained his wife over alleged infidelity. Despite stringent laws, most crimes against women in India go unreported, many offenders go unpunished, and the wheels of justice turn slowly, according to social activists who say successive governments have done little to ensure the safety of women and children.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/husband-chains-wife-over-alleged-infidelity-madhya-pradesh-111129697.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 16:41:29 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">husband-chains-wife-over-alleged-infidelity-madhya-pradesh-111129697</guid></item><item><title>Security tightened in Kashmir's border areas before elections</title><description>Rajouri (Jammu), Mar.21 (ANI): Police in the border areas of Jammu and Kashmir have tightened security to thwart any militant attack ahead of general elections. Parliamentary elections will be held in nine phases between April 7 and May 12. Deputy Inspector General of Police of the Rajouri-Poonch Range Ashok Kumar Atri said: "Recently, we had received specific information that a militant was also sent on trial basis on the Indian side and we had recovered AK-47 and IED from him. We have become more alert and vigilant after the arrest of the militant." The Kashmir region has witnessed numerous militant attacks, insurgency and infiltration attempts from across the border in the last two decades.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/security-tightened-kashmirs-border-areas-elections-111129933.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 16:41:29 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">security-tightened-kashmirs-border-areas-elections-111129933</guid></item><item><title>NCW member Nirmala Samant praises court sentencing of rape convicts</title><description>New Delhi, Mar.21 (ANI): National Commission of Women (NCW) member Nirmala Samant on Friday praised a Mumbai court for handing down life terms to convicts involved in the rapes of two women last year. "This was an expected verdict, and hence, we want to laud the Mumbai Police for the manner in which they presented the evidence and witnesses in order to strengthen the case against the culprits, which helped the court to take a right decision finally. But in this case, a prompt FIR and a conviction took place," Samant said. "We praise the victim who came ahead and lodged a complaint, (and) she spoke highly about the manner in which the media raised the case," Samant added.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/ncw-member-nirmala-samant-praises-court-sentencing-rape-111129691.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 16:41:29 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">ncw-member-nirmala-samant-praises-court-sentencing-rape-111129691</guid></item><item><title>Expert panel next week to select new Andhra capital: Ramesh</title><description>New Delhi, March 21 (IANS) A five-member expert committee will be constituted next week to select capital of the residuary state of Andhra Pradesh, said union minister Jairam Ramesh. The Group of Ministers (GoM) on bifurcation of Andhra Pradesh met here Friday to review actions to be taken in the next few days. Ramesh told reporters after the meeting presided over by Union Home Minister Sushilkumar Shinde that an expert committee will be announced early next week. The central and the state governments are trying to complete all the works related to bifurcation before June 2, the day when Telangana and Andhra Pradesh will come into being.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/expert-panel-next-week-select-andhra-capital-ramesh-110405508.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 16:34:05 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">expert-panel-next-week-select-andhra-capital-ramesh-110405508</guid></item><item><title>Accused in Dalit massacre arrested in Bihar</title><description>Patna, March 21 (IANS) An accused in the 2000 massacre of 34 Dalits in Bihar was arrested Friday from a school in the state, police said. Nanbutan Sharma, accused in the massacre that took place in Aurangabad district's Miyapur village, was arrested by the police in Arwal district, about 100 km from here, police official Pankaj said. The accused was arrested following a tip off to police that he had changed his name to Amrendra Sharma and was working as a contractual teacher in a school, Pankaj said. Sharma, a member of the outlawed Ranvir Sena, was absconding since the massacre.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/accused-dalit-massacre-arrested-bihar-110404156.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 16:34:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">accused-dalit-massacre-arrested-bihar-110404156</guid></item><item><title>Complete Tejpal trial in 60 days, prosecution tells court</title><description>Panaji, March 21 (IANS) The prosecution in the Tehelka rape case Friday moved a formal application seeking to fast track the trial within 60 days.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/complete-tejpal-trial-60-days-prosecution-tells-court-102224846.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 15:52:24 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">complete-tejpal-trial-60-days-prosecution-tells-court-102224846</guid></item><item><title>Shakti Mills gang rape case: Court gives life imprisonment to all four convicts</title><description>Mumbai, Mar.21 (ANI): A Mumbai court on Friday sentenced four convicts to life imprisonment for raping a photo-journalist and a telephone operator in the deserted Shakti Mills compound. On Thursday, the court had held five men guilty in two cases of gang rape. The court convicted the five men for gang rape, conspiracy and offences under the Information Technology Act. The first case pertains to the gang rape of a 22-year-old photo-journalist who had gone to the deserted Shakti Mills compound with a male colleague on an assignment on August 22, 2013.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/shakti-mills-gang-rape-case-court-gives-life-100525519.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 15:35:25 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">shakti-mills-gang-rape-case-court-gives-life-100525519</guid></item><item><title>Four get life sentence in Shakti Mills gang-rape</title><description>Mumbai, March 21 (IANS) A Mumbai court Friday awarded life sentences to four men convicted for gang-raping a 19-year-old call centre employee in the Shakti Mills Complex on July 31, 2013. The four convicts are Vijay Jadhav (18), Qasim Hafiz Sheikh alias Qasim Bengali (20), Salim Ansari (27) and Mohammad Ashfaque Shaikh (26). On the evening of July 31, 2013, the victim, who had taken a shortcut through the Shakti Mills on her way to the Siddhivinayak temple with her boyfriend, was waylaid and attacked by five people, including the four convicts and a minor. Initially, she kept quiet about the incident but gathered courage to complain to police after the gang-rape of a 23-year-old journalist in the same premises on August 22, 2013.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/four-life-sentence-shakti-mills-gang-rape-094218894.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 15:12:18 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">four-life-sentence-shakti-mills-gang-rape-094218894</guid></item><item><title>Gul Panag files nomination papers to contest from Chandigarh</title><description>Chandigarh, Mar 21, (ANI) Aam Aadmi Party (AAP) leader Gul Panag on Friday filed her nomination papers here to contest in the Lok Sabha elections amidst cheer and fanfare.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/gul-panag-files-nomination-papers-contest-chandigarh-093721382.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 15:07:21 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">gul-panag-files-nomination-papers-contest-chandigarh-093721382</guid></item><item><title>Four get life sentence in Shakti Mills gang-rape case</title><description>Mumbai, March 21 (IANS) A Mumbai court Friday awarded life sentence to four of the five accused in the gang-rape of a 19-year-old call centre employee July 31, 2013 in the Shakti Mills Complex here. The accused were found guilty by Principal Sessions Judge Shalini Phansalkar-Joshi Thursday in one of the two gang-rape cases committed in the same premises. The quantum of sentence in the Aug 22 gang-rape case of a photo-journalist will be announced later as the prosecution has sought severe punishment for the three who are guilty in both the cases.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/four-life-sentence-shakti-mills-gang-rape-case-084004315.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 14:10:04 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://www.ians.in/">IANS India Private Limited/Yahoo India News</source><guid isPermaLink="false">four-life-sentence-shakti-mills-gang-rape-case-084004315</guid></item><item><title>J-K Govt. bags 'National Tourism Award' for 2012-13</title><description>Srinagar, Mar.21 (ANI): Much to the delight of the people of Jammu and Kashmir, the state has bagged the 'National Tourism Award' for 2012-13 in 'Best State-Comprehensive Development of Tourism' category. The award was given by the tourism ministry to the state, and it appreciated the achievements of the tourism sector of Jammu and Kashmir, which has developed by leaps and bounds due to stringent efforts by locals and the state government. A local businessman, Nazir Ahmad, said that more such awards will come and the government had to take up the responsibility of building the infrastructure. "Kashmir has a priority as it's a very beautiful place.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/j-k-govt-bags-national-tourism-award-2012-083937306.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 14:09:37 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">j-k-govt-bags-national-tourism-award-2012-083937306</guid></item><item><title>Chidambaram had lost election last time also: Subramanian Swamy</title><description>New Delhi, Mar.21 (ANI): Reiterating his charge against Finance Minister P. Chidambaram, Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) leader Subramanian Swamy on Friday said Chidambaram had lost the elections last time also, but the returning officer had made a false declaration about his win. "Chidambaram not contesting elections is clear as last time also he had lost. It was by manipulation and rigging that a false declaration was made by the returning officer that he has been elected," said Swamy. On Thursday, the Congress had fielded Finance Minister P Chidambaram's Karti Chidambaram from Sivaganga constituency in Tamil Nadu.</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/chidambaram-had-lost-election-last-time-subramanian-swamy-075450940.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:24:50 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">chidambaram-had-lost-election-last-time-subramanian-swamy-075450940</guid></item><item><title>Congress leader Satpal Maharaj joins BJP</title><description>New Delhi, Mar. 21 (ANI): Senior Congress leader from Uttarakhand, Satpal Maharaj, today resigned from the party and joined the Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP).</description><link>http://in.news.yahoo.com/congress-leader-satpal-maharaj-joins-bjp-075450492.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2014 13:24:50 +0530</pubDate><source url="http://aniin.com/">ANI</source><guid isPermaLink="false">congress-leader-satpal-maharaj-joins-bjp-075450492</guid></item></channel>
</rss>
<!-- fe1.global.media.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Fri Mar 21 21:27:59 UTC 2014 -->
